휴지 사왔나?
Did we get paper towels?
우리가 사러 나갔던 거?
You mean the thing
we went to the store for?
아니
Nope.
얘들아, 선물이야!
Hey, I got you a present!
와, 어디에 숨겨 놨던 거야?
Oh, my goodness, where did you hide it?
결혼식 때 주문했는데
드디어 도착했어!
I ordered it for your wedding
and it's finally here!
이러지 않아도 됐는데...
You didn't have to get us anything..
난 좋아! 크다! 얼른 풀어 보자!
I love it! It's huge! Let's open it!
- 팩맨 부인 게임기잖아!
- 세상에!
-It's a Ms. Pac-Man machine!
-Oh, my God!
어디다 둘지 몰라서
거기다 뒀어
I didn't know where to put it.
- 손님 방에 두면 되겠다
- 그래
-We can put it in the guest bedroom.
-Yeah, okay.
난 여기가 좋은데
I kind of like it here.
이거 좋아해?
Do you like it?
난 어린 시절을 거의
오락실에서 보냈는데
I practically spent my
entire childhood at the arcade.
- 이걸 두 번째로 좋아했어
- 첫 번째는 뭐야?
-This was my second favorite.
-What's your first?
- 이름이 생각 안나
- 뭐하는 거였는데?
-I don't remember the name.
-Well, what did it do?
동전을 넣고 손잡이를 돌리면
사탕이 나오는 거야
You'd put a quarter in,
pull some handles and win a candy bar.
자판기?
A vending machine?
그러지마, 항상 이겼다구!
Don't feel bad for me.
I won every time!
프렌즈 시즌 8
'조이와 레이첼의 데이트'
여기 있었구나
I'm so glad you guys are here.
고생물학과에서
무슨 일이 있었게?
Guess what happened
in the paleontology department.
로스가 우릴 봤을까?
몰래 나갈까?
Do you think he saw us,
or can we still slip out?
학과장인 뉴먼 교수가 은퇴해서...
Professor Newman, the department head,
is retiring, so..
- 학과장이 됐구나!
- 내가 고급반을 가르치게 됐어!
-They made you head of the department!
-I'm teaching his advanced class!
내가 왜 학과장이 안됐지?
Why didn't I get head
of the department?
축하해, 고급반 가르치고 싶어
했잖아
Great. You've always wanted
to teach an advanced class.
응, 내가 원하던 거야
No, I know. It's really exciting.
This is the break I've been waiting for.
뉴먼 교수는 법원 명령을
I'm not sure a court-ordered
detox program..
원했던 건지는 모르겠다
was the break
Professor Newman was waiting for.
어쨌거나
But, hey.
레이첼, 데이트 나가는데
좋은 레스토랑 추천해 줘
Hey, Rach, I got a big date.
Do you know a good restaurant?
폴스 카페, 음식도 좋고
로맨틱해
Paul's Cafe. It's got great food
and it's really romantic.
고마워
Great, thanks.
그 다음엔 포시즌에 가서
음료수 마셔
Then take her to the
Four Seasons for drinks.
아니면 시내에 가서
재즈를 듣던가
Or go downtown
and listen to some jazz.
춤추러 가는 게 좋겠다!
Or dancing. Oh, take her dancing!
도대체 섹스는 언제
하라는 거야
You sure are naming
a lot of ways to postpone sex.
나도 데이트 하고 싶다
근사한 레스토랑에도 가고
I miss dating. Dressing up,
going to a fancy restaurant.
아주 오랫동안 못하겠지
정말 재밌는데
I won't be able to do that for so long.
And it's so much fun.
앉아서 아기 낳는 거
걱정하는 일도 재밌긴 하지만
Not that sitting around
worrying about giving birth isn't fun.
있잖아
나랑 데이트 하자
Hey, you know what?
Why don't I take you out.
뭐? 임신한 여자랑
데이트 하겠다고?
You don't want to date
a pregnant lady.
그래, 같이 즐기고 오자
Yes, I do. We're gonna
have a good time.
출산, 제왕절개...
애기 머리 늘어나는 거
I'll take your mind off of childbirth,
and C-sections..
다 잊는 거야
and baby heads stretching out..
좋아, 그러자
Okay, I'll go with you.
- 재미 있을거야
- 좋았어
-It will be fun.
-All right.
노우, 노우! 예스!
No, no! Yes!
저거 좀 봐 줄래
Would you look at that.
내가 다 이겼어
안됐다
I knocked off all your top scores.
How sad.
좋아, 내가 다음이야
Okay, I'm next.
다른 게임 시작하지 마
내가 다음 순서야!
Don't start another game.
I'm next! Phoebe?
글쎄, 다 이기니까
잘 안들려
Sorry, I couldn't hear you
over all the winning.
- 피비가 게임을 독점하고 있어
- 바보 같은 게임이야
-Phoebe's hogging the game.
-It's a stupid game.
자기가 못하니까
바보 같다고 하는 거야
You think it's stupid because
you suck.
내가 아니라 이 기계가 바보야
I don't suck. It sucks.
자기도 바보야
You suck.
이 기계가 문제면
내가 가질게
If this game is gonna cause problems,
I should keep it.
아냐, 좋아해
No, I love it. It is a great present.
집에 가서 감사 카드나
기다리고 있어
Why don't you go home and wait
for the thank-you card?
- 왜 그렇게 이 게임에 집착해?
- 초콜렛 바도 안 나오잖아
-Why do you want to play this game?
-It doesn't spit out a Clark Bar.
좋아, 피비
의자에서 비켜
Okay. Phoebe, that's it.
Out of the chair.
피비!
챈들러!
Phoebe!
Chandler!
여자들 싸움에 안낄래
사랑 놀이로 바뀌나 봐야지
No, no. This is a girl fight.
I'm hoping it will turn into love-play.
내가 잘못 했어
Okay, look.
Honey, I'm sorry..
내가 너무 공격적이었어
이 게임이 너무 좋아서
I'm acting hostile. I don't mean to.
It's just that I love this game so much..
나도 해보고 싶었던 거야
that I would just like
the chance to play it too.
와우, 니가 치와와처럼
머리에서 짖어대는데도
Wow, it's amazing how well I can play
with you yapping around my head..
이렇게 잘 하는거 봐
like a Chihuahua.
이제 못 참아, 챈들러
나 좀 도와줘
All right, that's it. Chandler,
help me get her out of the chair.
챈들러, 얼른
Chandler, come on.
조이, 좀 나가 봐!
Joey, could you get that?
조이
Joey.
방에 있는 줄 알았더니
I thought you were in your room.
너 데리러 왔어
이건 너 주려고 가져온 거야
I'm picking you up for our date.
For you.
내가 제일 좋아하는 백합이네
고마워
Lilies. They're my favorite.
Thank you.
그리고 브라우니도 있어
And a brownie.
절반이지만...
Well, half a brownie.
실은 봉지만 남았어
Actually, it's just a bag.
꽃가게가 너무 멀어서...
It's a long walk from the flower shop
and I felt faint, so..
대단해! 정말 데이트 같아
This is so great! I actually feel
like I'm on a real date.
입덧도 하고 속옷도 이런 걸...
But I have morning sickness and
I have on underwear that goes up to..
입었지만...
there.
우리 진짜 데이트 하는 거야
Hey, come on. This is a real date.
집이 좋네
So nice place you got here.
축구공, 피자 박스도 있고
Football. Pizza box.
플레이보이도 구독하고
딱 내 스타일인데...?
Oh, a subscription to Playboy.
My kind of woman.
내 룸메이트 거야
That's my roommate's.
한 번 만나보고 싶은데
괜찮은 친구 같은 걸
I'd like to meet him.
He sounds like a standup guy.
나에 대해 보호본능이 강해서
조심해야 할 걸
He's protective of me,
so you'd better watch yourself.
룸메이트 잘 생겼어?
Your roommate, is he good-looking?
그에게서 손을 뗄 수가 없지
안그래?
Must be tough to keep your hands
off him.
게이인 거 같아
I'm pretty sure he's gay.
아니야! 게이 아냐!
왜 그래?
No! No, he's not! Why are you trying
to ruin the game?
이것이 그리리의 지배 이론으로
이어지는 거죠
Which brings us back
to Greely's Theory of Dominance.
오늘 수업 끝입니다
That's it for today.
프리맨 빌딩이 어딘지 알아요?
Does anyone know where
the Freeman Building is?
애비뉴 A에 있는 새 건물인데요
It's the new building on Avenue A.
그렇게 멀어?
10분 후에 강의인데...
That's across town.
I'm teaching there in 10 minutes.
안 될걸요
Dude, that's not gonna happen.
비켜요! 비켜!
Move it! Move it!
선생이에요!
Hey! I'm the teacher!
안녕하세요
Hello.
약간 늦었죠?
와, 엄청 늦었네
Sorry I'm a little late.
Whoa, a lot late.
먼저 제 소개를 할게요
Well, let me start
by introducing myself.
저는 겔러 교수입니다
I'm Professor Geller.
결론을 말하자면...
So to sum up..
저는 겔러 교수이고
오늘 수업 마치겠습니다
I'm Professor Geller.
Good job today.
- 필레 미뇽에는 뭐가 나와요?
- 삶은 야채요
-What comes with the filet mignon?
-Steamed vegetables.
야채 대신에...
Instead of the vegetables..
저 3파운드짜리 랍스터를
is there any way that I could
substitute the..
먹을 수 있는 방법이 있나요?
three-pound lobster?
둘 다 가져다 주세요
You know what? Bring her both.
저도 같은 걸로요
And I'll have the same.
와, 정말 근사한 데이트
같은데
Wow, this is shaping up
to be a pretty good date.
참, 깜박했다
방값을 안냈어
I almost forgot.
I didn't pay you the rent.
데이트에 집중해
No roommate stuff. It's a date.
야, 조이가 데이트에서
어떻게 하는 지를 보겠군
Wow, so I get to see what
Joey Tribbiani is like on a date.
특별한 코스가 있어?
Have any moves?
그냥 평소대로 하는 거지
만약 나를 안 좋아하면...
No, I'm just myself,
and if they don't like me for..
미안, 정리 좀 하고
I'm sorry, I couldn't even
get through that.
알아, 얼른 말해 봐
I knew it. Tell me your moves.
좋아
All right.
먼저...
Well..
어느 팬이 내 테이블로 와인을
한 병 보내게 하는 거야
I start by having a bottle of wine
sent to my table from a fan.
세상에, 효과가 있어?
Oh, my God. And that works?
이렇게 말해야 돼 "당황스럽네요
평범하게 살고 싶은데"
If you add, "This is embarrassing.
I just want to have a normal life."
가여운 유명인사구나
You poor little famous man.
이건 어떤가 봐
Okay, how about this one?
밤까지 기다렸다가
키스하려고 했는데
I was gonna wait until the end
of the night to kiss you..
당신이 너무 아름다워서
그렇게 못할 것 같아요
but you're just so beautiful,
I don't think I can.
정말 죽인다!
Oh, my God!
환상적이야!
나도 거의 넘어갔다니까
Wow, that was fantastic!
I almost leaned in. Really.
너는 어떻게 하는지 말해봐
So tell me one of your moves.
좋아
All right.
어디서 자랐어요?
So where'd you grow up?
겨우 그거야?
That's your move?
얼굴이 예쁘니 다행이다
Boy, Rach, you're lucky you're hot.
- 얼른 대답이나 해
- 퀸즈
-Come on, just answer the question.
-Queens.
부모님하고는 사이가 좋았어요?
Were you close to your parents?
- 아빠하고는 별로...
- 어머, 왜요?
-With my mom. Not so much my dad.
-Why not?
글쎄요, 거리감이 좀 있어요
I don't know.
There's just this distance.
둘 다 아닌 척 하지만
분명히 그래요
We both try to pretend it's not there,
but it is.
힘들겠네
It's gotta be rough.
정말 그래요
때로는...
Yeah, it's really tough.
Sometimes I think..
와우!
Wow!
괜찮은데!
Nice move!
- "어디서 자랐어요?" 간단하네
- 고마워
-"Where'd you grow up?" So simple.
-Thank you.
화장실 좀 다녀올게
Now, excuse me.
I'm gonna use the restroom.
- 이제 내가 걷는 걸 보는 거야
- 그렇지! 정말 간단하다!
-Now you're watching me walk away.
-Yes, I am! So simple!
- 내가 오늘 뭐 했는지 알아?
- 샤워하고 면도는 안했고...
-You won't believe what I did today.
-Clearly not shower or shave.
종일 이거 해서
이제 통달했어
I played this all day,
and now I rule.
이름을 "챈들러 부인"으로
바꿔야할 걸
They should change the name
to "Ms. Chandler."
안 바꾸길 바라지만
Although, I hope they don't.
내가 바보처럼 일하러 간 동안
집에서 팩맨부인을 했다구?
You stayed home and played Ms. Pac-Man
while I went to work like a chump?
1등부터 10등까지 모두 나야
피비를 눌렀어, 하이 파이브!
I got the top 1 0 scores. I erased
Phoebe off the board. High-five!
손이 왜 그래?
What is the matter with your hand?
게임을 8시간이나 했더니
I played for eight hours.
점수 좀 봐봐
It'll loosen up. Check out the scores.
이름도 봐
다 욕으로 해놨어
Also, look at the initials.
They're dirty words.
- 챈들러, 왜 그랬어?
- 굉장하잖아
-Chandler, why would you do that?
-Because it's awesome.
이게 영리한 짓이라고 생각해?
You think it's clever?
처음 세 자밖에 못 쓰니까
A, S, S 다음부턴 머리를 써야 돼
They only give you three letters,
so after A-S-S, it is a challenge.
그래도 할만큼 했네
But clearly you're up to the task.
- 이건 욕이 아니잖아
- 저거랑 합쳐 봐
-This one's not dirty.
-Put it together with that one.
오우
Oh.
이거 안 지우면
하나는 앞으로 구경 못할 걸
If you don't clear this off,
you won't get one of those from me.
내일 벤이 오니까
다 지워야 해
Ben's coming over tomorrow.
This can't be there.
- 무슨 뜻인지도 모를텐데
- 7살이고 바보가 아니야
-He won't know what they mean.
-He's 7, not stupid.
- 최근에 벤이랑 이야기해 봤어?
- 코드 뽑아 버릴거야
-Have you talked to him lately?
-I'm gonna unplug it.
안돼, 내가 한 일을 보여줄 수
없잖아, 회사에서처럼
I'll have nothing to show for my day.
Like work.
안돼!
No!
저거 봐! 아직 있어!
Hey, look! It's still there!
완전 구식 ROM 칩인가 보네!
This thing must have some kind
of primitive ROM chip!
와우
욕설에 컴퓨터 용어까지
Wow. The dirty words
and the computer talk.
당신의 가장 멋진 모습이다
This is just the coolest
you've ever been.
- 점수를 이겨야 돼
- 손톱으로?
-You gotta beat your scores.
-With the claw?
됐어, 내가 할게
이걸 없애 버려야지
Fine, I'll do it.
We gotta get this off.
자기가 손가락 뽑기 가르쳐서
캐롤이 아직도 화났단 말야
Carol's still upset that
you taught him "Pull my finger."
손가락 뽑아 봐... 손이 이상해!
Pull my finger. My hand is messed up!
- 안 할거야
- 하나만 골라 봐
-I am not gonna answer that.
-Oh, come on. Just pick one.
모니카와 피비, 챈들러, 로스
중에서...
Between Monica, Phoebe,
Chandler and Ross..
꼭 때려야 한다면
누굴 선택할거야?
if you had to,
who would you punch?
친구끼리 무슨 소리야
아무도 안 때릴거야
We're friends.
I wouldn't punch any of them.
챈들러?
Chandler?
응, 이유는 나도 몰라
Yeah, but I don't know why.
- 오늘 정말 기분 좋다!
- 나도!
-I'm having a wonderful time!
-Me too!
- 생애 최고의 데이트야
- 나도!
-This is the best date I ever had.
-I know!
너무 웃어서 내 코에서
와인 나오는 거 봤어?
I laughed so hard. Did you
see the wine come out my nose?
거기 있던 사람은 다 봤을 걸
Joey, I think everybody saw it.
섹스 말고도 이렇게
즐거울 수 있는 걸 처음 알았어
I never knew I could enjoy
the non-sex part of a date so much.
왜냐면 나하고 데이트를
안했기 때문이지
That's because you have never
been on a date with me before.
나 이상하게 보지 마
All right. Now don't judge me.
대개 남자가 갈 때까지 기다리는데
너니까 이걸 지금 하는 거야
I normally wait till my date leaves,
but I'm ripping into the swan.
너도 나 이상하게 보지 마
Okay, then you don't judge me.
브라우니에 붙은 셀로판지
빨아 먹을 거니까
I'm gonna suck on the cellophane
from that brownie.
알았어
Oh, yeah.
그래서 조이 트리비아니의
마지막 코스는 뭐야?
So tell me, what are Joey Tribbiani's
end-of-the-night moves?
여자가 키스해 주기를 원하면
Well, if I want the girl to kiss me..
먼저 내 입술을
아주 섹시하게 만들어
first, I make my lips
look irresistible.
어떻게 한 거야?
How do you do it?
아무한테도 말하지마
Now you can't tell anyone, but..
립그로스를 바르는 거야
I put on shiny lip balm.
- 그렇구나
- 다들 불나방처럼 빨려 들지
-Oh, my God.
-Like a moth to a flame, I tell you.
- 이제 네 차례야
- 말 안할래
-Okay, now you go.
-No, I don't want to tell you.
- 왜?
- 좀 민망해
-Why not?
-It's embarrassing.
딸기맛 립그로스보다
심한 거야?
More embarrassing than
shiny raspberry lip balm?
아까 내가 딸기맛이라고 말했나?
I didn't say raspberry before, did I?
말해 봐, 레이첼
Just tell me, Rach. Just tell me.
좋아
Okay.
일어서 봐
All right, stand up.
문 앞에 서면...
Well, when we're at the door..
내 입술을 살짝
상대방 입술에 눌러
I lightly press my lips
against his.
그리고 1초 정도 몸에 기대
Then move into his body,
just for a second.
그런 다음 이 소리를 내는 거야
And then I make this sound:
아무것도 아닌 것 같지만
분명히 효과가 있어
It doesn't sound like anything,
but it works.
정말 효과가 있네
Oh, yeah. That would work, yeah.
이제 자야겠다
오늘 정말 즐거웠어
All right, I gotta go to bed.
I had such a wonderful time.
나도
Me too.
50분이나 늦었어?
기어갔냐?
You were 50 minutes late?
Did you crawl?
뛰어 갔어, 진짜 멀어
No, I ran, okay? It's really far.
사람들이 도대체 왜 그렇게
"비켜"라는 말을 못알아 듣는거야?
When did people stop understanding
"Get out of my way"?
택시 타지 그랬어?
Why didn't you take a cab?
일방통행에 체증도 심해서
두 배는 더 걸려
With the traffic and one-way streets,
it'd take me twice as long.
1주에 수업이 3번이나 있는데
무슨 제트기가 있는 것도 아니고
And I have class three times a week.
Who am I, Rockefeller?
계속 못할 것 같은데
You won't be able to keep doing this.
내가 못하면 다른 사람한테
수업을 넘길거야
If I don't, they'll take the class
away from me.
가족 신문에 이미 알렸는데...
And I put it in my family newsletter.
- 뭐?
- 봤잖아, 겔러 옐러 신문
-Your what?
-You've seen it, The Geller Yeller.
아... 와우
Right. Wow.
지름길 알아냈어
이번엔 안 늦을거야
I figured out a faster route.
I'm sure I can make it this time.
차에 좀 치일 수 있지만
I just can't be afraid
to get a little bit hit by cars.
- 안녕
- 왔어?
-Hey.
-Hi!
어제 쿠조 이야기 기억 나?
Remember when we talked about Cujo?
쿠조를 안 봤다니
어떻게 그럴 수 있지?
I can't believe you haven't seen Cujo.
너무 그러지마
시민 케인 도 아니잖아
Relax, it isn't Citizen Kane.
시민 케인
끝까지 본 적 있어?
Have you ever sat through
Citizen Kane?
진짜 지루하지
근데 대단한 거 같아
Yeah, it's really boring.
But it's, like, a big deal.
암튼, 쿠조를 빌려보면 어떨까
생각하는데...
Anyway, I was thinking
about renting Cujo.
지금 빌려오자
Well, let's do it tonight.
- 데이트 있다고 하지 않았어?
- 맞다
-Don't you have that big date?
-Oh, right.
- 조이, 뭐 하나 물어봐도 돼?
- 응
-Hey, Joey, can I ask you something?
-Yeah.
우리 데이트 후에
이상한 거 없었어?
After our date, did you feel weird?
너도 그랬어?
나 깜짝 놀랬잖아, 왜 그랬지?
Oh, my God. You did too?
It freaked me out. What was that?
글쎄, 내 생각엔
랍스터 때문인 거 같애
I don't know. I'm kind of thinking
it was the lobster.
아... 랍스터...
Oh, yeah. Yeah, the lobster.
- 밤새 토했어
- 나도... 밤새...
-I was up sick all night.
-Me too. All night.
정말? 근데 몰랐네
Really? We didn't cross paths.
어... 왜냐면...
Yeah, well, that's because..
내가 방에 있었거든
I stayed in my room.
방에서 토했어
You don't want to look
in my hamper.
아...
Okay, I got that.
저기를 빠져 나와서
여기로 올 거야
I'll escape there.
I'll come back here.
화이팅 팩맨부인
All right. Come on, Ms. Pac-Man.
이 망할 할망구?!
Well, you're just a little bitch,
aren't you?!
얘들아?
Hey, you guys?
지난 번에 내가 너무 독점해서
미안해
I'm sorry that I was
hogging the game before.
근데 지금 자리 안 비켜주면
폭력을 쓸지도 몰라
But if you don't get off soon,
I will cut you.
이런!
니 친구들 이름이 왜 이러냐
Oh, my God! Your friends have
some unfortunate initials.
챈들러가 한 거야
They're all Chandler.
챈들러가 이렇게 잘 한다구?
Chandler couldn't get this good.
그렇지, 대가를 치르긴 했지만
I did. But it came at a price.
벤이 오니까 이거 다 지워야 해
Ben's coming, and he can't see this.
7살이면 볼 건 다 봤지
By age 7, kids have
already seen orgies.
나만 그런 거야?
Was it just me?
그래서...
So..
시간이 없어요
we're about out of time.
오늘은 새로운 것을
많이 배웠죠
Now, I know I've given
you a lot of new information.
양이 좀 많긴 하지만
And it may seem
a little overwhelming.
오늘 수업에서
But, if there's one thing..
한 가지 기억해야 할 것이
you need to take away
from class today..
있다면
it's that..
공룡은 다시 돌아오지 않는다는
것입니다
dinosaurs ain't never coming back.
그럼 다음 시간에 봅시다
I'll see you next time.
해냈다! 제 시간에 왔어!
Yes, I made it! I'm on time!
자, 여러분...
Okay, why don't we all..
23페이지를 펴세요
open our books to page 23..
어디냐면...
where..
에...
where you will see..
빨간 점이 가득 있는...
a bunch of red spots.
23페이지 먼저 읽고 계세요
저는...
Okay, why don't you all start to read
while I..
당황스럽네요
This is so embarrassing.
평범하게 살고 싶은데
I just want to have a normal life.
와우, 아주 비싼 와인인데요
Wow, that's an expensive
bottle of wine.
그래요?
It is?
내 팬들은 보통 이러지 않는데
That's funny, my fans
don't normally do that.
괜찮아요?
마음이 딴 데 있는 사람 같아요
Are you all right?
You seem a little distracted.
아, 괜찮아요...
No, no, I'm fine. It's just..
하나 물어봐도 돼요?
Hey, can I ask you something?
오래 알고 지내던 사람을...
Have you ever looked at someone
you know..
갑자기 다른 각도로 보게
된 적 있어요?
and suddenly seen them
in a different way?
뒤에서요?
You mean like from behind?
네... 그렇죠
Yeah. That's exactly it.
어떤 남자가 뒷모습은
아주 평범해 보이더라구요
I saw this guy from behind,
and he seemed totally normal.
그런데 딱 돌아서니까
스티븐 볼드윈인 거 있죠!
And then he turned around
and it was Stephen Baldwin!
아, 네...
Yeah.
제 말을 완전히 이해하셨네요
So you know exactly what I mean.
그럼요!
Totally! Wow.
- 잠깐 실례할게요
- 네
-Would you excuse me?
-Sure.
- 피비! 완전히 불붙었구나!
- 말 시키지마!
-Phoebe! You're on fire!
-I know!
잘 한다!
You can do it!
- 손대지마!
-Don't touch me!
-Don't touch her!
왼쪽! 오른쪽! 오른쪽!
Go left! Go right! Go right!
못하겠어! 안돼!
I can't! I can't!
안돼! 이 망할...
No! You son of a..
피비?!
Phoebe?!
어, 안녕 벤
안돼, 기계 쳐다보지 마!
Oh, hi, Ben.
No, don't look at the machine!
드디어 왔네!
쿠조보고 있었어
Thank God you're home!
I'm watching Cujo.
- 혼자?
- 응! 이 개 왜 이런거야?
-Alone?
-Yes! What is wrong with this dog?
쿠조가 차에 몸을 날리는
장면 봤어?
Did you get to the part where Cujo
throws himself at the car?
농담 아니야
진짜 이 개 왜 이래?
No, seriously,
what's wrong with the dog?
참, 데이트는 어떻게 됐어?
Wait, what happened to your date?
잘 안됐어
Oh, it didn't work out.
- 영화 같이 볼래?
- 좋아, 그러자
-Want to watch the rest of the movie?
-Oh, okay. Yeah.
내가 이런 말 할 줄 몰랐는데...
I never thought I'd say this..
이 개가 죽으면 좋겠어
but I hope this dog dies.
거기서 뭐해?
여기 앉아, 날 보호해 줘야지
What are you doing?
Sit here. Protect me.
어, 그래야지
Oh. Sure, yeah. Why not?
좋아
Okay.
- 쟤야, 쟤! 쟤가 쿠조야!
- 알아
-That's him, that's him! That's Cujo!
-I know.
괜찮을 거야
It's gonna be okay.
어떡해... 이제 뭐 하려는 거야?
못 보겠어
Oh, my God. What's he gonna do now?
I can't watch.
넌 어떻게 본 거야?
안 무서워?
How can you watch this?
Aren't you scared?
완전히 겁에 질렸지
Terrified.
모두 왔어요?
전 좀 일찍 왔습니다
So is everybody here?
I got here a little early, myself.
시작합시다
Let us begin.
해드로사우리드는 두 곳에서
주로 발견되었는데...
Now, the hadrosaurids have been
unearthed in two main locations.
이곳...
Here..
그리고...
and..
이곳이죠
here.
히드로사우르스는...
Now, as for the hydrosaurs..